Guide to the New York University Archives Biographical Files MC.317
New York University Archives
- Duncan, Erika, undated (Box 52)
- Dunfee, Nora, undated (Box 52)
- Dunkel, Alexander, undated (Box 52)
- Dunkin, Erica, undated (Box 52)
- Dunlaing, Colm, undated (Box 52)
- Dunlap, Robert, undated (Box 52)
- Dunmore, Charles William, undated (Box 52)
- Dunn, Charles W. Dr., undated (Box 52)
- Dunn, John, undated (Box 52)
- Dunn, Harris, undated (Box 52)
- Dunn, Marie, undated (Box 52)
- Dunnigan, Frank J. 40C, undated (Box 52)
- Durham, Edward J., undated (Box 52)
- Durgin, Don, undated (Box 52)
- Durra, Zeina, undated (Box 52)
- Durrell, Samuel, undated (Box 52)
- Duscher, Harriet G.'77 C, '36 Ed., undated (Box 52)
- Dusenby, Elizabeth, undated (Box 52)
- D'Usseau, Arnaud ( - 1990), undated (Box 52)
- Duster, Tron, undated (Box 52)
- Dutra, Enrico Gaspar, undated (Box 52)
- Dutka, Solomon, undated (Box 52)
- Dutton, John M., undated (Box 52)
- Duyckinck, Evert A., undated (Box 52)
- Duyckinck, George, undated (Box 52)
- Dworkin, Ronald, undated (Box 52)
- Dworkin, Martin, undated (Box 52)
- Dwyer, Dean Charles A. Fac. C, undated (Box 52)
- Dwyer, James, undated (Box 52)
- Dystel, Oscar '35C, undated (Box 52)
- Dziejma, Raymond, undated (Box 52)
- E, Weinan, undated (Box 52)
- Eagles, Jordan, undated (Box 52)
- Eagleton, Clyde, undated (Box 52)
- Eames, David B., undated (Box 52)
- Earhart, Amelia, undated (Box 52)
- Easley, Carol Maureen, undated (Box 52)
- Eastman, Crystal, undated (Box 52)
- Eastman, Susan, undated (Box 52)
- Ebel, Isabel C. (1934 alumna), undated (Box 52)
- Ebersole, Suzanne, undated (Box 52)
- Ebon, Martin, undated (Box 52)
- Ebsworth, Miriam, undated (Box 52)
- Echlin, Francis Asbury, undated (Box 52)
- Eckel, Rhea M., undated (Box 52)
- Ecker, David W. Dr., undated (Box 52)
- Eckert, William, undated (Box 52)
- Eckhouse, Joseph L., undated (Box 52)
- Edel, Leon, undated (Box 53)
- Edelman, Sergei, undated (Box 53)
- Edelman, Ethel and Irvin A., undated (Box 53)
- Edelsburg, Nathan, undated (Box 53)
- Edelstein, J.M., undated (Box 53)
- Edelstein, Marcus, undated (Box 53)
- Eder, Phanor J., undated (Box 53)
- Edes, Everita, undated (Box 53)
- Edey, Helen Winthrop, undated (Box 53)
- Edison, Beatrice, undated (Box 53)
- Edison, Thomas A., undated (Box 53)
- Edmonson, Thomas, 1899, 1938 (Box 192, Folder 16)
- Edmundson, Thomas W., undated (Box 53)
- Edson, Jarvis B., undated (Box 53)
- Edwards, Charles, undated (Box 53)
- Edwards, Flora, undated (Box 53)
- Edwards, Gail, undated (Box 53)
- Edwards, Harold, undated (Box 53)
- Edwards, Herbert W., undated (Box 53)
- Edwards, James Valentine, undated (Box 53)
- Edwards, Paul, undated (Box 53)
- Edwards, Phil (Commerce '30), undated (Box 53)
- Egan, Jenny, undated (Box 53)
- Egan, Patrick J., undated (Box 53)
- Egerer, Joel, undated (Box 53)
- Egnatz, Ben, undated (Box 53)
- Ehmann, Howard W. '31E, undated (Box 53)
- Ehrenfeld, Sylvain Dr., undated (Box 53)
- Ehrenkranz, Joel '61L, undated (Box 53)
- Ehrenkranz, Shirley M., undated (Box 53)
- Ehrenreich, Alden, undated (Box 53)
- Ehringer, Frank J. '43 E, undated (Box 53)
- Ehrenpreis, Leon Dr., undated (Box 53)
- Ehrenreich, R., undated (Box 53)
- Ehret, Wm F., undated (Box 53)
- Ehrman, Frederick L., undated (Box 53)
- Ehrlich, Otto H., undated (Box 53)
- Ehrgot, John D. '17E, undated (Box 53)
- Ehrsam, Theodore, undated (Box 53)
- Eichhorn, Adolph, undated (Box 53)
- Eichhorn, Harold '29A, undated (Box 53)
- Eickelman, Dale, undated (Box 53)
- Eide, Elizabeth, undated (Box 53)
- Eisen, Cliff, undated (Box 53)
- Eisenberg, Ronda, undated (Box 53)
- Eisenbud, Merril '36 E, undated (Box 53)
- Eisenberg, Gerson, undated (Box 53)
- Eisenstein, Jethro M, undated (Box 53)
- Eisgruber, Christopher L., undated (Box 53)
- Eisenhardt, Emil, undated (Box 54)
- Eisenstein, Miriam, undated (Box 54)
- Eisler, Colin, undated (Box 54)
- Elfenbein, Julien, undated (Box 54)
- Eliaz, Dr. E., undated (Box 54)
- Eliscu, Jean I., undated (Box 54)
- Elkin, Stanley, undated (Box 54)
- Ellenbogen, Joan L., undated (Box 54)
- Ellenson, Nadine, undated (Box 54)
- Ellerin, Betty Weinsberg '50W, '52L, undated (Box 54)
- Elliffe, Dick, undated (Box 54)
- Elling, Emil Von, undated (Box 54)
- Ellinwood, Frank Field, undated (Box 54)
- Elion, Gertrude Belle, undated (Box 54)
- Elliot, Sheldon D., undated (Box 54)
- Ellis, Brooks F., undated (Box 54)
- Ellis, Edward Robb, undated (Box 54)
- Ellis, Larry, undated (Box 54)
- Ellis, Margaret Holben, undated (Box 54)
- Ellis, Perry '63R, undated (Box 54)
- Ellison, Alfred, undated (Box 54)
- Ellison, Ralph, undated (Box 54)
- Ellwood, Carol, undated (Box 54)
- Ellsworth, Raymond, undated (Box 54)
- Ellsworth, Elmer Brown, undated (Box 54)
- Ellsworth, Theodore Dart, undated (Box 55)
- El-Sabat Anwar, undated (Box 55)
- El-Sadat, Jehan, undated (Box 55)
- El-Shawan, Salwa A., undated (Box 55)
- Emerson, Ralph Waldo, undated (Box 55)
- Emerson, Robert S., undated (Box 55)
- Emir of Qatar, undated (Box 55)
- Emmerich, Frederick J., undated (Box 55)
- Engi, Kenneth, undated (Box 55)
- Ende, Nathan '29W, '31L, undated (Box 55)
- Engel, Susan, undated (Box 55)
- Engberg, Holger L., undated (Box 55)
- England, Suzanne, undated (Box 55)
- Englander, Roger, undated (Box 55)
- Engle, David, undated (Box 55)
- Engle, Hannah, undated (Box 55)
- Engle, Robert, undated (Box 55)
- Enright, Anne, undated (Box 55)
- Enroth, Carl Edward, undated (Box 55)
- Engleman, Gus, undated (Box 55)
- Enselman, Isidor, undated (Box 55)
- Ensler, Eve (Tisch), undated (Box 55)
- Epps, Alfred S., undated (Box 55)
- Eppston, Harold, undated (Box 55)
- Epstein, Albert, undated (Box 55)
- Epstein, Daniel, undated (Box 55)
- Epstein, Harold, undated (Box 55)
- Epstein, Harry '20E, undated (Box 55)
- Epstein, Helen, undated (Box 55)
- Epstein, Richard, undated (Box 55)
- Erdman, Jean, undated (Box 55)
- Erdman, Robert, undated (Box 55)
- Erdman, John F. '87M, undated (Box 55)
- Erickson, Gordon, undated (Box 55)
- Erim, Kennan T. (Dr), undated (Box 55)
- Errico, Elizabeth Haggerty '69, '76, undated (Box 55)
- Ernst, Frederic, undated (Box 55)
- Ervin, John, undated (Box 55)
- Esformes, IRA '71E, undated (Box 55)
- Esibill, Nancy, undated (Box 55)
- Esposito, Ronald, undated (Box 55)
- Esquirol, John Henry '20A, '23L, undated (Box 55)
- Esquirol, Joseph A. 17A 20L, undated (Box 55)
- Esserman, Paul, undated (Box 55)
- Estreicher, Samuel, undated (Box 56)
- Eswein, Liz, undated (Box 56)
- Mel, Ettinger, undated (Box 56)
- Ettinger, Curtis T. '63L, undated (Box 56)
- Ettelbrick, Paula L., undated (Box 56)
- Ettinger, Richard '15C, undated (Box 56)
- Ettinger, Richard P., undated (Box 56)
- Ettinger, Virgil P. '21C, undated (Box 56)
- Ettinghausen, Richard, undated (Box 56)
- Eustace, Nicole, undated (Box 56)
- Eustice, James S., undated (Box 56)
- Evans, Lester U., undated (Box 56)
- Evans, Dr. Seymour '49 W., '53D, undated (Box 56)
- Evans, Vilma I '56Ed., undated (Box 56)
- Euerhart, Rex, undated (Box 56)
- Everson, William K., undated (Box 56)
- Ewald, Peter K. '45A, '47G., undated (Box 56)
- Ewen, Robert, undated (Box 56)
- Ewing, Parmer L., undated (Box 56)
- Fabricant, Solomon, undated (Box 56)
- Facio, Gonzalo J., undated (Box 56)
- Fackler, Clarence, undated (Box 56)
- Faek, Irving, undated (Box 56)
- Fafunwa, Dr. a. Babs '51 Ed., undated (Box 56)
- Fagin, Claire, undated (Box 56)
- Fagg, John E., undated (Box 56)
- Fairbank, Diane, undated (Box 56)
- Fairchild, Henry Pratt, undated (Box 56)
- Falconi, Toni Muzi, undated (Box 56)
- Fales, DeCoursey, undated (Box 56)
- Falk, Anna M., undated (Box 56)
- Falk, Irving A. '43W, '71ER., undated (Box 56)
- Falk, Minna R., undated (Box 56)
- Falk, Max, undated (Box 56)
- Falk, Ze 'Ev W., undated (Box 56)
- Falkenhain, Patricia, undated (Box 56)
- Falknor, Judson F., undated (Box 56)
- Falmagne, Jean-Claude, undated (Box 56)
- Falnes, Oscar J., undated (Box 57)
- Farber, Saul Joseph, undated (Box 57)
- Farfel, Aaron, undated (Box 57)
- Farkas, George, undated (Box 57)
- Farkas, Ruth Lewis, undated (Box 57)
- Farma, Williams, undated (Box 57)
- Farr, Walter, undated (Box 57)
- Farrell, Mary C., undated (Box 57)
- Fass, Elias N., undated (Box 57)
- Fass, Rita D., undated (Box 57)
- Fassin, Eric, undated (Box 57)
- Fasteau, I. Jack, undated (Box 57)
- Fatt, Arthur '25L, undated (Box 57)
- Favill, Josiah Marshall, undated (Box 57)
- Fayerweather, John, undated (Box 57)
- Fedde, Norman, undated (Box 57)
- Federman, Barry '34E., undated (Box 57)
- Federman, Hyman L '34C, '39 GBA, undated (Box 57)
- Federsen, Jack F., undated (Box 57)
- Fiedler, Leslie, undated (Box 57)
- Fein, Arnold L '33L, '31 WSC, undated (Box 57)
- Fein, Harry D. '36M, undated (Box 57)
- Feinberg, Maxine A. '77W, '80D, undated (Box 57)
- Feinman, Joanna, undated (Box 57)
- Feinsot, Aaron, undated (Box 57)
- Feldman, Jill '80, undated (Box 57)
- Feldman, Jonathan, undated (Box 57)
- Feldman, Noah, undated (Box 57)
- Feldman, Robert Lee, undated (Box 57)
- Feldman, Samuel M., undated (Box 57)
- Feldman, Susan, undated (Box 57)
- Fellner, Tamar, undated (Box 57)
- Feldman, Yael, undated (Box 57)
- Fellowes, P.F.M., undated (Box 58)
- Fellows, Hugh, undated (Box 58)
- Felton, Barbara, undated (Box 58)
- Felzenberg, Leonard I '55L., undated (Box 58)
- Fendrick, David, undated (Box 58)
- Feukel, Milton O. (Dental), undated (Box 58)
- Fennelly, Brian, undated (Box 58)
- Fennell, Michael Martin, undated (Box 58)
- Ferguson, M. Carr, undated (Box 58)
- Ferguson, Niall, undated (Box 58)
- Ferguson, Wallace K., undated (Box 58)
- Ferguson, Walter, undated (Box 58)
- Ferhadi, Ahmed, undated (Box 58)
- Fernald, Henry Barker, undated (Box 58)
- Fernald, Henry B. '01A, undated (Box 58)
- Fernald, Henry B., Jr. '33E, undated (Box 58)
- Fernandez, Louise Surra, undated (Box 58)
- Fernandez, Oscar, undated (Box 58)
- Ferrari, Carlo Dr., undated (Box 58)
- Ferrero di Rocaferrera, Guiseppe M. Dr., undated (Box 58)
- Ferris, Family, undated (Box 58)
- Ferris, Isaac (Election as Chancellor), undated (Box 58)
- Fertig, Lawrence '19A, undated (Box 58)
- Festinger, Trudy B., undated (Box 58)
- Fetherston, John T., undated (Box 58)
- Fichandler, Zelda, undated (Box 58)
- Field, Hartry, undated (Box 58)
- Field, Robert L. '74, undated (Box 58)
- Fielder, Edgar Russell ℅ 1970, undated (Box 58)
- Fields, Morey R., undated (Box 58)
- Fields, Murray M., undated (Box 58)
- Feigel, Fred J., undated (Box 58)
- Feinberg, Mortimer, undated (Box 58)
- Ficken, Frederick A., undated (Box 58)
- Findley, G. L., undated (Box 58)
- Fine, Vivian, undated (Box 58)
- Fink, Burton, undated (Box 58)
- Fink, Harold, undated (Box 58)
- Fink, Michael, undated (Box 58)
- Finkel, Asher, undated (Box 58)
- Finkelstein, Jerry '29W, undated (Box 58)
- Finkelstein, Norman, undated (Box 58)
- Finley, John Huston, undated (Box 58)
- Finkler, Steven A., undated (Box 58)
- Finley, Karen, undated (Box 58)
- Finn, David, undated (Box 58)
- Finney, David, undated (Box 58)
- First, Harry, undated (Box 58)
- Fishbach, Marilyn, undated (Box 58)
- Fischer, Dietrich, undated (Box 58)
- Fischler, Stanley I., undated (Box 58)
- Fisher, Avery '29W, undated (Box 59)
- Fish, Barbara, undated (Box 59)
- Fisher, Edwin L., undated (Box 59)
- Fischer, John, undated (Box 59)
- Fischer, Leon H., undated (Box 59)
- Fischer, Leon Harold, undated (Box 59)
- Fischer, Mitchell S., undated (Box 59)
- Fisher, Richard L., undated (Box 59)
- Fishman, James J., undated (Box 59)
- Fishman, Sidney, undated (Box 59)
- Fisk, Stanley, undated (Box 59)
- Fisz, Marek, undated (Box 59)
- Fitch, David, undated (Box 59)
- Fitzgerald, Garret, undated (Box 59)
- Fitzgibbon, William C., undated (Box 59)
- Fitzmaurice, Thomas J., undated (Box 59)
- Fitzpatrick, Kathleen, undated (Box 59)
- Flanagan, Eugene J.T., undated (Box 59)
- Flanders, Ralph, undated (Box 59)
- Flane, Gibert, undated (Box 59)
- Flapan, Israel M., undated (Box 59)
- Flax, Carol, undated (Box 59)
- Flaxman, Seymour L., undated (Box 59)
- Fleck, Henrietta, undated (Box 59)
- Fleischer, Rita M., undated (Box 59)
- Fleischman, Edward, undated (Box 59)
- Fleisig, Allen, undated (Box 59)
- Fleming, Andrew, undated (Box 59)
- Fleming, Daniel, undated (Box 59)
- Fleming, Robert S. Dr., undated (Box 59)
- Fleri, Alfonso N., undated (Box 59)
- Fletcher, Joseph, undated (Box 59)
- Flexner, Kurt f. Dr., undated (Box 59)
- Flicker, Norman, undated (Box 59)
- Flinn, Christopher J., undated (Box 59)
- Flittel, Hessel Howard, undated (Box 59)
- Flom, Joseph H., undated (Box 59)
- Flora, Holly, undated (Box 59)
- Flores, Juan, undated (Box 59)
- Flores, Thomas (Political Economist), undated (Box 59)
- Florio, Steven T., undated (Box 59)
- Floy, Michael (Diary Excerpt 1833-37), undated (Box 59)
- Fluellen, Thom, undated (Box 59)
- Fluharty, George, undated (Box 59)
- Fluss, Pola, undated (Box 59)
- Flynn, Carol Houlihan, undated (Box 59)
- Flynn, Joseph Leo '26 C, undated (Box 59)
- Flynn, Timothy J., undated (Box 59)
- Fogarty, Bryce M., undated (Box 59)
- Fogel, Dr. Samden H., undated (Box 60)
- Fogle, French, undated (Box 60)
- Fogler, Raymond, undated (Box 60)
- Foley, Ether V., undated (Box 60)
- Folcarelli, John W. '74W., undated (Box 60)
- Foley, Richard, undated (Box 60)
- Foltz, Ann-Marie, undated (Box 60)
- Fonda, Bridget, undated (Box 60)
- Foote, Paul Sheldon, undated (Box 60)
- Foote, Thelma, undated (Box 60)
- Ford, Kristina, undated (Box 60)
- Ford, Tom, undated (Box 60)
- Foreman, Carl, undated (Box 60)
- Forester, John J., undated (Box 60)
- Foristall, Lynn E. '57 GBA, undated (Box 60)
- Forman, Donald J. '48C., '56L, undated (Box 60)
- Forrest, Charles Dorsey, undated (Box 60)
- Forrester, Robert, undated (Box 60)
- Fortunoff, Alan M., undated (Box 60)
- Fortunoff, Louis, undated (Box 60)
- Foster, Henry H., undated (Box 60)
- Foster, Major B., undated (Box 60)
- Foster, Richard, undated (Box 60)
- Foster, Rose Marie Perez, undated (Box 60)
- Foster, Stephen Collus, undated (Box 60)
- Fowkes, Robert A. '34A., '35G, undated (Box 60)
- Fowler, Burton P., undated (Box 60)
- Fowler, Elizabeth M., undated (Box 60)
- Fowler, George, undated (Box 60)
- Fowlkes, John W., undated (Box 60)
- Fox, Donald T. '56L, undated (Box 60)
- Fox, Eleanor M., undated (Box 60)
- Fox, Raymond E. '57 GBA, undated (Box 60)
- Fox, Herbert, undated (Box 60)
- Fox, Levi, undated (Box 60)
- Fox, Marcia Rose, undated (Box 60)
- Fox, Sherwood D., undated (Box 60)
- Fox, Sylvan, undated (Box 60)
- Foye, Arthur B '14C., undated (Box 60)
- Foye, Arthur B., undated (Box 60)
- Franc, Max, undated (Box 60)
- France, Harry C., undated (Box 60)
- Francis, Samuel Ward, undated (Box 60)
- Frank, Thomas, undated (Box 61)
- Franco, James, undated (Box 61)
- Frank, Beatrice, undated (Box 61)
- Frank, Charles R. '48E, undated (Box 61)
- Frank, George, undated (Box 61)
- Frank, Harry B., undated (Box 61)
- Frank, Howard, undated (Box 61)
- Frank, Martin M. '23L., undated (Box 61)
- Frank, Stanley, undated (Box 61)
- Frankel, Eliot, undated (Box 61)
- Frankel, Gene, undated (Box 61)
- Frankel, Howard L. (Dr), undated (Box 61)
- Frankel, L.R., undated (Box 61)
- Franklin Jr. George S., undated (Box 61)
- Fraser, Evelyn Dawn, undated (Box 61)
- Fraser-abder, Pamela, undated (Box 61)
- Frazer, Alfred, undated (Box 61)
- Fraser, James, undated (Box 61)
- Frazier, E. Franklin (Dr.), undated (Box 61)
- Frazier, Ruppert, undated (Box 61)
- Freccero, John, undated (Box 61)
- Frederick, Alan, undated (Box 61)
- Frederick, Jim, undated (Box 61)
- Frederick, Robert F., 1986 (Box 192, Folder 18)
- Fredericks, Carlton, undated (Box 61)
- Fredenthal, Peter C. '54A, '64L, undated (Box 61)
- Freed, Fredericic C., undated (Box 61)
- Freedman, Hallie, undated (Box 61)
- Freedman, M. Joel (Dr.), undated (Box 61)
- Freedman, Richard D., undated (Box 61)
- Freech, Louis, undated (Box 61)
- Freeland, James J., undated (Box 61)
- Freeman, Herbert, undated (Box 61)
- Freeman, Joshua B., undated (Box 61)
- Freeman, Morgan J., undated (Box 61)
- Freidson, Eliot, undated (Box 61)
- Freiman, Gerald V., undated (Box 61)
- Freiman, Maurice E. (Dental), undated (Box 61)
- Freilich, Michael L., undated (Box 61)
- Frelinghuysen, Theo, Hon. LL..D, undated (Box 62)
- Frelinghuysen, Theodore (Relation to Rutgers), undated (Box 62)
- Freud, Marc, undated (Box 62)
- Friedenberg, Dr. Frederick F. '48D, undated (Box 62)
- Friedlander, Percy '20E., undated (Box 62)
- Friedlaender, Walter, undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Don, undated (Box 62)
- Friedrichs, Kurt O., undated (Box 62)
- Freitag, Werner, undated (Box 62)
- Freiwald, Dorothy Pearce W5C '48, '63 Ed., undated (Box 62)
- French, Joseph Milton, undated (Box 62)
- French, Thomas Clayton, undated (Box 62)
- Freund, Peter F., undated (Box 62)
- Freund, Thomas, undated (Box 62)
- Freund, William C., undated (Box 62)
- Freudmann, Felix R., undated (Box 62)
- Frey, George F., undated (Box 62)
- Frey, Henry, undated (Box 62)
- Frey, Walter G., undated (Box 62)
- Fri, James L., undated (Box 62)
- Fribourg, Michel (Prof. European Studies), undated (Box 62)
- Frichner, Tonya Gonnella, undated (Box 62)
- Friedan, Betty, undated (Box 62)
- Friedberg, Marjorie Dr., undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Adam I. '68 G., undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Jay B., undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Jeffrey M., undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Joel M., undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Lewis, undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Milton, undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Paul '31W, '37 L., undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Richard, undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Samuel Dr., undated (Box 62)
- Friedman, Anton, undated (Box 62)
- Friedson, Eliot, undated (Box 62)
- Friel, Brian, undated (Box 62)
- Friend, James P., undated (Box 62)
- Fritz, Alexander, undated (Box 62)
- Fritz, Charles A., undated (Box 62)
- Froatz, Frances, undated (Box 62)
- Fromm, Erich, undated (Box 62)
- Frommer, Dr. Harvey '57C, '62Ed. '72Ed, undated (Box 62)
- Frontera, Jim, undated (Box 192, Folder 17)
- Frosch, William A., undated (Box 62)
- Frost, John E. (NYU Librarian), undated (Box 62)
- Frost, Robert, undated (Box 62)
- Froum, Stuart J., undated (Box 62)
- Fruchter, Norm, undated (Box 62)
- Fruman, Norman, undated (Box 62)
- Fry, Vera S., undated (Box 62)
- Frusciano, Thomas, undated (Box 62)
- Frydman, Roman, undated (Box 62)
- Frye, Douglas, undated (Box 62)
- Fryer, Douglas, undated (Box 62)
- Fryscak, Milan, undated (Box 62)
- Fryer, Douglas, undated (Box 62)
- Fuchs, David, undated (Box 62)
- Fuchsberg, Jacob D., undated (Box 62)
- Fuerst, Harold T. Dr., undated (Box 63)
- Fuller, Harold DeWolf, undated (Box 63)
- Fuller, R. Buckminster, undated (Box 63)
- Fulmer, Terry, undated (Box 63)
- Fulrath, Logan, undated (Box 63)
- Fung, Florence Y.M. (Tsai), undated (Box 63)
- Furmanski, Philip, undated (Box 63)
- Fusfeld, Herbert I., undated (Box 63)
- Futhey, Bruce, undated (Box 63)
- Gabler, Earl R., undated (Box 63)
- Gabor, Stanley, undated (Box 63)
- Gabrielson, Milton (Dr.), undated (Box 63)
- Gadsby, Edward, undated (Box 63)
- Gage, Louis Waite (Mrs), undated (Box 63)
- Gage, Martin A., undated (Box 63)
- Gaifman, Hana Arie, undated (Box 63)
- Gaines, Edythe, undated (Box 63)
- Gainsbrugh, Martin, undated (Box 63)
- Gair, Harry A., undated (Box 63)
- Gale, Cedric, undated (Box 63)
- Gale, Leonard Dunnell, undated (Box 63)
- Gallagher, Richard, undated (Box 63)
- Gallatin, Albert, undated (Box 63)
- Gallaudet, Thomas H., undated (Box 64)
- Galloway, Alexander, undated (Box 64)
- Gangeni, J.R., undated (Box 64)
- Gannon, Joseph W. '55, undated (Box 64)
- Gannon, Joy M. '80W., undated (Box 64)
- Gans, David, undated (Box 64)
- Gans, Paul J., undated (Box 64)
- Ganz, Nancy, undated (Box 64)
- Garbus, Martin, undated (Box 64)
- Garcia-Mazas, Jose, undated (Box 64)
- Gardner, Howard, undated (Box 64)
- Gardner, Merle, undated (Box 64)
- Garfield, Shoshanna, undated (Box 64)
- Garland, David William, undated (Box 64)
- Garniez, Bernard, undated (Box 64)
- Gardiner, John A., undated (Box 64)
- Garelik, Sanford, undated (Box 64)
- Garelli, Jacques, undated (Box 64)
- Garibaldi, Marie L., undated (Box 64)
- Garretson, Albert, undated (Box 64)
- Garrett, James F. '49Ed, undated (Box 64)
- Garrett, Ray Jr., undated (Box 64)
- Garrison, Lloyd K., undated (Box 64)
- Garvey, George, undated (Box 64)
- Gartenstein-Ross, Daveed, undated (Box 64)
- Garvin, Edwin L., undated (Box 64)
- Gasparitsch, Edward, undated (Box 64)
- Gaster, Theodore H., undated (Box 64)
- Gately, Dermot, undated (Box 64)
- Gates, Hailey, undated (Box 64)
- Gates Jr., Henry Louis, undated (Box 64)
- Gates, John fitzgerald, undated (Box 64)
- Gates, Linda, undated (Box 64)
- Gates, Moody B '97A, undated (Box 64)
- Gaudnek, Walter, undated (Box 64)
- Gaunt, Robert, undated (Box 64)
- Gay, Wilson A., undated (Box 64)
- Geacintov, Nicholas (Chemistry), undated (Box 64)
- Geddes, Robert, undated (Box 64)
- Gehm, Rudolph, undated (Box 64)
- Geistfeld, Mark, undated (Box 64)
- Geither, Timothy, undated (Box 64)
- Geizmar, Arthur B., undated (Box 64)
- Gelb, Arthur '46W, undated (Box 64)
- Gelb, Lawrence '19A, undated (Box 64)
- Gelb, Pete (Nathaniel) '59A, undated (Box 64)
- Gelber, Ida, undated (Box 64)
- Gelber, S. Michael, undated (Box 64)
- Geldorf, Lillian, undated (Box 64)
- Geldorf, Irving L. '16E, undated (Box 64)
- Geller, Abraham, undated (Box 64)
- Geller, Lawrence D., undated (Box 64)
- Geller, Molly S., undated (Box 64)
- Gellman, Irving Peter, undated (Box 64)
- Geneen, Harold S. '34C, undated (Box 64)
- Gennardo, Joseph F., undated (Box 64)
- Genns, D.M., undated (Box 64)
- George, Zelma Watson, undated (Box 64)
- Georgiadis, Hourmouzis, undated (Box 64)
- Georgiou, Constantine, undated (Box 64)
- Gephardt, Richard, undated (Box 64)
- Gerard, George, undated (Box 64)
- Geraciotti, Larry, undated (Box 64)
- Gerard, Robert E., undated (Box 64)
- Gerassi, John, undated (Box 64)
- Gerdes, John, undated (Box 64)
- Gerdes, Victor, undated (Box 65)
- Germanotta, Stefani Joanne, undated (Box 65)
- Gershenson, Charlotte B., undated (Box 65)
- Gershon, Samuel, undated (Box 65)
- Gershoy, Leo, undated (Box 65)
- Gerson, Kathleen, undated (Box 65)
- Gerstenberg, Charles W., undated (Box 65)
- Gertler, Menard (Dr.), undated (Box 65)
- Gerstenberg, Karl, undated (Box 65)
- Gessner, Robert, undated (Box 65)
- Gettler, Alexander O., undated (Box 65)
- Gettler, Joseph Daniel, undated (Box 65)
- Ghansi, M.S., undated (Box 65)
- Ghent, Emmanuel, undated (Box 65)
- Giacomelli, E., undated (Box 65)
- Giannini, Mario, undated (Box 65)
- Giardino, Alfred A., undated (Box 65)
- Gibbs, Josiah Willard, undated (Box 65)
- Gibian, Gerald Z. '52 A., '62 L., undated (Box 65)
- Giblin, Edward '50, undated (Box 65)
- Gibson, Danielle, undated (Box 65)
- Gibson, Paul Jr., undated (Box 65)
- Gibson, Quentin, undated (Box 65)
- Giddings, Horace Alpheus, undated (Box 65)
- Giddon, Donald, undated (Box 65)
- Gidlund, Erick Ray, undated (Box 65)
- Giel, Charles P. '49 M., undated (Box 65)
- Gigante, Vincent, undated (Box 65)
- Gilbert, Charles (Dr.), undated (Box 65)
- Gilbert, John V., undated (Box 65)
- Gilbert, Lord, undated (Box 65)
- Gilbert, M. Shanara, undated (Box 65)
- Gilbert, Morris, undated (Box 65)
- Gilbert, Paul D., undated (Box 65)
- Gilbert, Paul D., undated (Box 65)
- Gilbert, Ralph W., undated (Box 65)
- Gilbride, Judith, undated (Box 65)
- Giles, Harry, undated (Box 65)
- Gillers, Stephen, undated (Box 65)
- Gillett, Ezra H. Rev. D.D., undated (Box 65)
- Gillett, William Kendall (1st. Spanish Professor), undated (Box 65)
- Gillers, Stephen, undated (Box 65)
- Gillespie, Karen R., undated (Box 65)
- Gilliard, Steven Jr., undated (Box 65)
- Gilligan, Carol, undated (Box 65)
- Gilligan, Vince, undated (Box 65)
- Gilloon, James V. Jr., undated (Box 66)
- Gilman, David, undated (Box 66)
- Gilman, Jane Prizant, undated (Box 66)
- Gilmore, George, undated (Box 66)
- Gilmour, Lloyd S., undated (Box 66)
- Gilroy, Joseph, undated (Box 66)